<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abdul Rafay</title>
    <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Abdul Rafay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 22:34:46 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://syedabdulrafay.com/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Cyclistic Data analysis</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/projects/divvy_bike_sharing_2019/divvy_bike-sharing/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 22:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/projects/divvy_bike_sharing_2019/divvy_bike-sharing/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Cyclistic is a bike-share company based in Chicago, USA. Its users are both the subscribers with annual membership and customers without any membership. The bikes can be unlocked from one station and returned to any other station in the system anytime.
The goal is to understand how both the types of users use the service differently to target appropriate marketing campaign and increase the number of subscribers. The data for year 2019 was used for this project, available here https://divvy-tripdata.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three Trials</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/story/three-trials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 22:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/story/three-trials/</guid>
      <description>There was a monastery on a long-lost land that taught the world’s most gifted students the secrets of the universe. There, Grandmaster held Book of Eternal Knowledge which had secrets to everything known and unknown. Once every hundred years, Grandmaster would come out of hiding and offer the disciples a chance to earn that Book.
They were given a choice to either take a single word from Book in exchange for all the years they had served at the monastery, or they could accept a challenge to win the complete text.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apology</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/story/apology/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/story/apology/</guid>
      <description>0005 “You know, cities are different; you hate it being there and feel lonely when you go away!” Krishan said as he threw the three of spades before him.
“Yeah, right”, Razaq replied and laid the four of spades on his pile of cards.
“That’s a donkey, old boy,” and handed Razaq one card from his hand and the three of spades lying before him.
“Ohh, my bad! I keep forgetting.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eulogy for 2020</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/blog/eulogy/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/blog/eulogy/</guid>
      <description>You and I are so similar, broken, marred with regrets of things that happened, and longings for things that never would be—we are both more words and fewer deeds, but it was never your fault; I did this to the both of us.
You are, the lava, a never-ending flow from the heart of the universe itself, creeping, burning, brighter than the brightest of suns, the sweet-child of One, One who forsook us all, and made you the lord in His stead.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hero returns!</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/hero-returns/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/hero-returns/</guid>
      <description>Trumpets beat
roses and jasmines
shower
from above
incense burns, hiding
the smell
of blood underneath
the white shroud
and trumpets drown
wails of
the son, the daughter
the mother, the father
and the widow
all the countrymen hail
the death of their
martyr.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Poem</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/poem/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/poem/</guid>
      <description>Hello this is
a new poem,
screw you!.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sandglass</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/sandglass/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/sandglass/</guid>
      <description>You came to me—a dream
gently—sinking in a warm
blonde fall of sand—hourglass
drowning me ever deep—grains
on the tongue, I taste the sun
the universe—my bare skin
melts—your hands keep hold
of me—the fall—I wake up
you are gone.
Footsteps on an endless shore
fading—waves sweeping off
the memory of your walk—run
to catch your path—run—to seek
refuge in you—run—to the end
of everything—there is no end
for days—months— years, I run</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Soot</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/soot/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/poetry/soot/</guid>
      <description>A small flame twinkles
it flickers as the wind blows
in the darkness—it rests
it has your name written all over
I had buried it deep
long ago, in the hope
its light would cease
to burn me
that time would turn it
into ash too
as it does to everyone
and everything
yet it is there
as new as it had been
the day I buried it
and its soot has turned</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Travel Gallery</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/blog/mytravels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 Mar 2021 20:34:46 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/blog/mytravels/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I am Abdul Rafay</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/detail/</guid>
      <description>A Creator, Writer, Traveler, and Climate Researcher.
I am fond of exploring distant lands, mountain tops, and forests, the unseen where nobody walks. It brings me close to my roots, connecting me to the mother earth, the origin of all life. So I keep looking for ways to pay respects to life.
But man’s greed for more has gone too far. His destructive hands have mutilated our ecosystems. The invasive industrialization that man calls advancement now threatens all life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Abdul Rafay</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/summary/</guid>
      <description>A Writer, Traveler, and Climate Researcher. I am fond of exploring distant lands, mountain tops, and forests, the unseen where nobody walks. It brings me close to my roots, connecting me to the mother earth, the origin of all life. So I keep looking for ways to pay respects to life.
Being a professional engineer, I have become more conscious of my own environmental impacts. My workplace mainly dealt with plastic products, so I had to find something new, a job that wasn’t a part of the problem, a place that took responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
