<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on Abdul Rafay</title>
    <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on Abdul Rafay</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I am Abdul Rafay</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/detail/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/detail/</guid>
      <description>A Creator, Writer, Traveler, and Climate Researcher.
I am fond of exploring distant lands, mountain tops, and forests, the unseen where nobody walks. It brings me close to my roots, connecting me to the mother earth, the origin of all life. So I keep looking for ways to pay respects to life.
But man’s greed for more has gone too far. His destructive hands have mutilated our ecosystems. The invasive industrialization that man calls advancement now threatens all life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I&#39;m Abdul Rafay</title>
      <link>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/summary/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2017 17:39:21 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://syedabdulrafay.com/about/summary/</guid>
      <description>A Writer, Traveler, and Climate Researcher. I am fond of exploring distant lands, mountain tops, and forests, the unseen where nobody walks. It brings me close to my roots, connecting me to the mother earth, the origin of all life. So I keep looking for ways to pay respects to life.
Being a professional engineer, I have become more conscious of my own environmental impacts. My workplace mainly dealt with plastic products, so I had to find something new, a job that wasn’t a part of the problem, a place that took responsibility.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
